import { QuestionType } from "../../components/question/multipleChoice";

export const orderOfOperationQuestion1Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is the value of 3+5x23 + 5 x 23+5x2?",
  options: ["16", "13", "10", "11"],
  answer: "16",
};

export const orderOfOperationQuestion2Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is the value of (8-3)x4(8 - 3) x 4(8-3)x4?",
  options: ["20", "32", "5", "28"],
  answer: "20",
};

export const orderOfOperationQuestion3Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is the value of 7+6÷2x37 + 6 ÷ 2 x 37+6÷2x3?",
  options: ["10", "16", "19", "13"],
  answer: "16",
};

export const orderOfOperationQuestion4Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is the value of 6x(2+3)÷36 x (2 + 3) ÷ 36x(2+3)÷3?",
  options: ["10", "15", "6", "12"],
  answer: "10",
};

export const orderOfOperationQuestion5Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is the value of 5+4x(6-2)÷25 + 4 x (6 - 2) ÷ 25+4x(6-2)÷2?",
  options: ["17", "13", "21", "14"],
  answer: "17",
};

export const orderOfOperationQuestion6Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is the value of 9-3+2x49 - 3 + 2 x 49-3+2x4?",
  options: ["26", "14", "10", "8"],
  answer: "14",
};

export const orderOfOperationQuestion7Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is the value of 8+(12÷4)x28 + (12 ÷ 4) x 28+(12÷4)x2?",
  options: ["14", "16", "12", "18"],
  answer: "14",
};

export const orderOfOperationQuestion8Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is the value of (10-3)x(8÷4)(10 - 3) x (8 ÷ 4)(10-3)x(8÷4)?",
  options: ["14", "28", "7", "17"],
  answer: "14",
};

export const orderOfOperationQuestion9Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is the value of 2x3+4x52 x 3 + 4 x 52x3+4x5?",
  options: ["26", "20", "23", "22"],
  answer: "26",
};

export const orderOfOperationQuestion10Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is the value of (7+3)÷2+5x2(7 + 3) ÷ 2 + 5 x 2(7+3)÷2+5x2?",
  options: ["14", "12", "11", "10"],
  answer: "15",
};
